おっ。
Yo, we meet again.
緊急停止信号です。
So we do...
お客様は　足元などに お気をつけください。
Long time, no see! Ya know?
何かあったのかな？ さぁ？
Can I ask you something?
[TEL] 俺だ…　来たか。
Sure, go ahead! Why didn't you dive underwater to escape?
ああ　間違いねえ！
You should have an advantage in the water.
うっ…　たった１人で　これだけの 人数を相手にできるのは
Don't tell me you can't swim.
奴らの他には　あり得ねえ！
Uh, well...
[TEL]　うっ！ ん？
It's the blood, right?
おい！　おい！ [TEL] クソ！
When they smell blood, your
buddies in the water go berserk
敵の正確な人数を把握しろ いいか　何としても止めるんだ。
and attack the injured, no matter who it is.
このビルに 絶対　近づけるんじゃ　ねえ！
With those wounds, if you went in there,
you'd be torn to shreds.
遅い！
I suppose that's one way to... Ikalgo, did you finish off the kid?
迎えは　まだ来んのか？ センリツとバショウという者だ。
No, we're still fighting! Who are you talking to?
現在　ヨークシン市内に入る
I screwed up!
全ての交通機関が 遮断されています。 足止めに遭っているのかと。
Right, you all can communicate via telepathy.
ここに ネオンがいては危険なんだ。
Talking to your boss? It's that guy
who was flying over me, right?
何とかして 避難させる方法はないか？
Wait, now look here...
先ほど手配した救急車が こちらに向かっております。 今しばらく　お待ちを。
Uh, so... You could say that's what I might be doing... Oh, sorry to interrupt you.
怪しい
Let me know if you learn anything.
ネオンと共にビルに侵入し 医者を呼んだ男
If he sees dozens of dragonflies
flying around inside a cave, the enemy would get suspicious...
クラピカ　救急車が来るまで
I won't be able to send my
Satellite Dragonflies inside.
娘のそばを離れるんじゃないぞ 分かったな。
Let's make a deal, then.
しかし　私は 「幻影旅団」抹殺の任務を…。
If you tell me about his power,
I'll spare your life.
あの時点では ネオンは帰る予定だった。
You have ten seconds to answer.
ネオンだけは 守り抜かねばならんのだ。 もうしばらく　ここにいろ！
Eight seconds left.
ヘッヘッへ…。
I wanted to be reborn a squid...
残念だぜ　意外と歯応えが　ねえ。 いや　期待し過ぎた俺が　バ…。
I would've given anything to have
been a Chiroteuthis imperator.
カ…。
Do you think octopi and squid are similar?
クッソ！ 噂以上にイカレてやがる。 たった１０人足らずで 真っ向から攻めて来やがるとは。
Squid are squidderific. I think they look divine!
まったく　ここは　いつから 戦場の真っただ中になったんだ？
I won't betray a buddy! Yeah, I could see that in your eyes.
患者は　どこかね？
I can only hope
あっ！ てめぇらが「旅団」の奴らじゃねえ という証拠は　ねえからな。
that in my next life, I'll be born a squid...
ついて来い。
Wh—
全員　改めさせてもらう。
Because you're a cool guy.
何だと!? てめぇ…。
In different circumstances,
we could've been friends.
ここじゃ ケータイが　つながらないし
You lowered your guard! Didn't think fish could jump, eh?
電車も　いつ動き出すか 分かんないし…。 しょうがねえ　走って行くか。
I'll crush you and the rock behind you! Come in, Ikalgo.
あぁ…。
Ikalgo!
こんなとこに隠れてねえで 戦いに出たら　どうだ？
No, he's been fighting...
それとも　実際に「旅団」が出て ビビったか？
with only his bare hands.
あぁ　クラピカには
Come on... Beg for your life.
私が「ここに　いろ」と 言ってしまったんだ。
Otherwise, it's no fun!
せっかく「十老頭」に 雇ってもらったのに
Or are you in too much pain to talk?
やっぱり　娘が心配でね。
Yeah, this is a relief. Huh?
告げ口などしませんよ。 しかし　高い金なんだろうから
Fighting scumbags like you is a lot easier. Huh?
役に立ってもらわねえと 困りますね。
I have no qualms about killing you.
ハハ…。 さすがに　何もしないわけには いかないと思います。
Yep! He was just a scumbag! That's why he was the decoy!
ビル内だけでも見回るべきかと。 そうだな。
I did it, Ortho-sama!
しかし　連絡したら すぐに戻って来い。
I've attached the badge!
娘の安全が　第一だ。
Coburn pulled it off!
了解しました。
Time to start the game.
いつまで　かかるんだよ！ おい！　一体　外は どうなってんだ！
Let's enjoy ourselves.
爆音が ここまで聞こえて来たぞ！ 競売は　いつ始まるんだ？
Damn, the bleeding won't stop...
説明しろよ　おめぇよ！ 今しばらくの　お待ちを。
I need to find an exit.
やるのか　やらねえのか はっきりしろ！ ここにいる全てが 組織の組長と大幹部のはず
A digital sound inside my head?
「旅団」の襲撃に対しても 揺るがぬ結束をアピールするために
Wha— What?
危険を承知で来ているが…
A fish? But I'm not in the water!
ケータイ返せ！ 外の様子が分かんねえ。
What's going on?
それから他の道具もよ！ 銃刀類の持ち込みは
I didn't sense anything!
慣例により 禁止されておりますので。
Again...
奴らが来たら　どうすんだ！ 素手で戦えってのか!?　あ？ さすがに　場が混乱して来たな
I didn't see anything or sense any
aura until the fish hit me!
オークショニアや 競売運営の責任者クラスでは
What's going on?
収拾できなくなるのも 時間の問題
This is bad.
[TEL] もしもし。 [TEL]　あっ　クラピカ？
I can't tell where the attacks are coming from.
よかった！　ようやく　つながった。
108 points.
[TEL]　ゴンか!? うん　今　大丈夫？ いや　悪いが忙しい こちらから　かけ直そう。
You have no idea what's going on?
[TEL]　ちょっと待って！ じゃあ　１分だけ。 [TEL]　用件だけ言うから。
I should say that you're
hearing my voice in your head.
俺とキルア　「旅団」に会った。 [TEL]　っていうか 捕まっちゃったんだけど…。
Well, if you survive long enough,
you'll figure out what's happening.
何を考えてるんだ　お前達は！
These are fish made from Nen.
[TEL]　相手が　どれだけ危険な連中か 分かってるのか!?
So why can't I sense them?
代わって。 分かってたつもりだったけど 会って痛感した。
Something must be triggering
them from somewhere else. That's the only possible explanation!
確かに奴らは強い 今の俺達だと　手も足も出ない。 だから クラピカの協力がいるんだ。
How else could I be attacked by
something I can't see or sense?
[TEL]　ふざけるな　お前達の 自殺行為に手を貸す気はない。
This is going well...
[TEL]　情報提供者は　ちゃんといる。 団員の能力についても 分かったことがある。
Well, have you determined
anything about these attacks?
[TEL]　くどい！　いいから 「旅団」から手を引くんだ！
Three... He can only materialize three fish at once.
[TEL]　奴らの１人を倒した鎖野郎って クラピカだろ？
After that, the fish will disappear.
[TEL]　あいつら　血眼で捜してるよ。
And the vivid colors of the
target he put on me...
お前が俺達のこと 仲間とも対等とも思えないなら
It can only mean one thing!
どんなて　使ってでも 協力してもらうぜ！　フン！
Your power involves
[TEL]　クラピカ。 あいつらの１人が 俺達の前で泣いたんだ。
Bingo. That's correct.
「仲間を殺した奴を許さない」って。
But the great thing about our power
is that figuring it out won't help you.
俺　それを見た時 無性に　やるせなくって…。
have no physical form until the
instant they pierce your flesh.
[TEL]　許せなかった…。
That makes it impossible to block them.
[TEL]　俺達も あいつらを止めたいんだ！
Incidentally, your left shoulder is 54 points.
頼むよ　クラピカ。
I have a dart board
[TEL]　こちらから　かけ直す。
that's linked to various parts of your body.
((お前が俺達のこと 仲間とも対等とも思えないなら))
Your right elbow is 27 points. Your right hand is 18 points.
((俺達も あいつらを止めたいんだ！))
99 points...
抜かるんじゃねえぞ！ ここまで熱が来る！
I can't hear your screams. Are you already dead?
誰か来る！ 銃　持ってるか？ ダメだ…　あいつら　強過ぎる。
The game's only just begun. Triple 6!
俺達じゃ　太刀打ちできねえ。
4! 13!
どのくらい　強いのかというと…！
Bravo! Brother, that was magnificent. You're on a roll.
このくらい！　イ！　イ！　イ!!
Naturally... Our lives are on the line...
アハハハ…！
This is how the Ortho siblings' power works.
クソが！ アハハハ…！ [TEL]　アハハハ…！
The sister creates a Nen badge, which activates after it's affixed to the target.
ああ　壊れちゃった 次のマシン　探さなきゃ。
That links the target to the dart
board created by the brother. Until the game ends, no one
can deactivate the badge, not even the Ortho Siblings.
大丈夫か!? 雇った暗殺者の死体が 見つかった！
When the brother's darts hit the board,
the target is attacked by needlefish.
すでに何者かが ビルの中にいるぜ！
There is no way to avoid this attack.
クソ！
That is because, until they've
hit the target's body, the needlefish do not exist.
相手にならねえ！ こら　逃げるな　戦え！
Needlefish De Darts! Death Games Death Games
Needlefish De Darts
[TEL] えい！ 一体　どうなってやがるんだ！ 俺だ！　応援が　全然来ねえぞ！ 何やってんだ！
But if the brother misses the board with the
final dart that decides the game's outcome, all of the damage the target has taken will transfer to the siblings.
[TEL]　もう着いても おかしくないはずだが。 [TEL]　俺達は　もうすぐ着く… うおっ！　うあっ！
We are invincible. That is because...
ん？
We are bound by the
strongest trust in the world.
まさか　集結させようとしている ２０００人近い構成員　全て やられちまってるのか？
Well, it seems the game's almost over. Why don't you tell him that?
どうする？　「旅団」の連中が すでに中に紛れてるんだぞ
No need to be that nice. If he were pleading for his life,
it'd be easier for me to focus.
俺だ　ビーンだ！ 「十老頭」に　つないでくれ！ 大至急だ！ 侵入者は　「旅団」に間違いない
Or if he were to give up
and beg me to kill him, or if he wanted to be a nihilistic hero
and said, "Not a bad way to die."
目的は　残りのオークションの品と 仲間の敵討ち
Those would help motivate me,
as I toss my darts.
((「仲間を殺した奴を 許さない」って)) 望むところだ！
But he'll just have to dread his impending
death, never knowing when it will end...
おい　いいかげんにしろよ！
Until he dies.
預けた得物を 武器をよこせっつってんだよ！
It's not...
慣例もクソもねえだろ！ 状況　分かってんのか!?
Damn...
知ってるぞ！ プロの暗殺者か何か知らねえが この中　うろついてるって いうじゃねえか！
This looks pretty bad...
そんな野郎に頼るくらいなら 俺らが　やってやるってんだよ！
I've lost way too much blood.
おぉ…！
I could die here, so no point in saving what's left.
わしは　ゼノ＝ゾルディックという者じゃ。
Now, then.
伝説の暗殺一家　ゾルディック家。
It's my final turn.
「十老頭」は こんな怪物を呼んでたのか。
Left ear.
現在　１人 このビル内に刺客が入っとる。
That sure gave him a big earring.
おたくらが雇った暗殺者の 何人かは　すでにやられた。
Right calf!
仮に　ぬしらが　それぞれ 武器を持ったとしても
Okay, time for the last throw. My brother, I trust you.
わしなら　この場で ７秒以内に全員殺せる。
I've got this.
どうじゃ？
Yay! Yay! Yay!
殺気も　ほんの一瞬で消し わずかな余韻すら残さない。
You're the best in the world! I'll go check his corpse. I'll come with you.
ふむ…。 仕方ない　「円」を使うか。
We should share some of the
meat with Coburn as a reward.
屋上から始めて 地下へ追い詰めるとしよう。
Aren't you gonna eat?
親父　大丈夫か？
Can I ask you something?
アホか　本気出せば ３００ｍは行けるわい。
What? What made you decide to trust me?
まったくもって 割に合わん仕事じゃて…。
It wasn't that I didn't trust you. I just didn't know why you were following me.
[TEL] あ…。
Then it's okay.
[TEL]　すぐ戻って来い！ ネオンのそばを離れるな！
I think I'm starting to lose it. He's strong, but he's just a kid.
はい　戻ります。 [TEL] クソ！
I'm putting my fate in the
hands of this clueless boy?
久しぶりだね。 俺を覚えているのか？
I can't even tell how much
power he really has...
忘れるわけない 仲間の１人をやられてるしね。 苦労したがな。
You hit him right in the forehead.
親父　気をつけろ 奴は他人の能力を盗む。
Flutter-sama, we've taken out the target. Really? That's excellent. I will tell Leol-sama that a
promotion is in order.
うお！
It's a suction cup from an octopus.
あ…。
How did you manage that trick?
ふぅ…。
Yeah, I didn't stop it.
２対１は　さすがにキツいな 俺の肌に傷をつけるとは なかなか　いいナイフだな
I just grabbed it, the moment it materialized at my head.
デザインから見て ベンズの中期型 ん？　あの形状…　毒か？
From what you were saying, I could tell you could hear my voice,
but you couldn't see me.
平気か？ 問題ない。 問題ないっすか… ０．１ｍｇで
I had plenty of time to switch out
the needle for a suction cup.
クジラとか 動けなくする薬なんだけど
H-Hold on...
他人の「念」を盗むか… 特質系じゃな。
No human has reflexes fast
enough to catch a dart!
もし　盗んだ能力を 自在に使えるとしたら 脅威じゃのう。 だが　それは 盗む際のリスクの高さを意味する。
Well, it wouldn't have been possible had
I not known where it would appear.
でなければ それだけの能力は得られまい。
But I knew exactly where and
when the last dart would hit.
４つか　５つ 盗むまでにクリアせねばならない 条件があるとみた。
The final dart must hit the board's
outer ring per double out rules.
ご名答 やりづらい　じいさんだ わしら２人と戦いながら その条件をクリアするのは至難。
And you were playing an 01—501 game.
つまり　わしらの能力が 戦いの最中に盗まれることは
You start with 501 points,
and the goal is to reach 0.
まず　あるまい。
These rules are used in professional competition.
毒ナイフでの威嚇が 良い証拠じゃ。
I n-never told you what rules I was using!
それも正解…　仕方ない
As soon as I knew you were playing darts,
my suspicions were confirmed.
シルバ　サポートせい わしが奴の動きを止めたら
your first dart hit double 4?
わしもろともで構わん　やれ。
The game starts by hitting the board's outer ring. A double in...
了解。
A sign that you were confident in your skill.
手にオーラを集中させた すさまじいポテンシャル
I subtracted your points from 501, and waited until your score was under 40.
あれで突かれたら 俺の防御力ではガードしきれない
At that point, I placed my hand in the 40-point area, my forehead.
マント…　具現化系か
from his skin to his brain
using the nervous system.
うん　厄介じゃのう 盗んだ能力の １つであろうが
He used Nen to ensure that, as soon
as the aura registered the dart, it sent a message directly to his
left hand, to grab the dart.
性質が分からぬ以上 うかつに攻撃できん
Do you have some history with darts? At age six, I mastered the game.
…と　普通の使い手ならば 思うじゃろうが
I've counted down from 1,440 points. It was part of my early training.
ヘヘっ　うりゃ！
What?
読めたわ
My body won't do what I tell it to...
さらに　自在に引き出し 使えるというもの
Wow...
しかし　その代償として 引き出した能力を使う際は
All this is my blood?
常に　その本を 手にしていなければならない
It feels like I'm taking a warm bath.
攻撃の気配が　ほとんど ないにもかかわらず
Wait, this isn't the time to think about that... I should get going.
わしに接近して 発動する性質の防御型か カウンター型の能力じゃろう
Crap... Now I feel cold...
故に　離れて戦えば 恐るるに足らん
Damn...
そして　隙を見て捕らえる
And after that last fight gave me a hint...
恐ろしい　じいさんだ
for improving my power.
一瞬にして　こっちの狙いは 全て見切られたか
Am I...
生け捕りは無理かな
going to die here?
本を閉じると 引き出した能力も消えるわけか
Gon... Sorry...
それにしても　大した使い手だ 親父の攻撃を 紙一重で　かわしながら
I wasn't any... help...
命を賭して動きを止めない限り 確実には仕留められない
Octopus... Don't call me an octopus!
今じゃ！　やれ！
It won't take long by underground waterway. Don't die before we get there!
フヘヘへ…！ フン！
I spared... your life... Now they'll be hunting you... I know that!
ヨークシンの街に 地響きが　とどろいた
After you told me, an octopus,
that I was a cool guy...
その震動が 予想外の展開を生むことを
After you said we could be friends...
クラピカは　まだ知らない
I couldn't let you die!